# Resume

**Brian Connors** 

31011 Jedediah Smith Rd

Temecula, CA. 92592

seahorse8789@gmail.com

## Summary

I have worked in the retail and pest control industry for a combined 11 years now. With those careers I have developed customer service and time management skills to complete projects on time. However, neither of these careers were not satisfactory to me. With that being said, I have decided to go back to school to learn computer programming.

### Education

| Temecula Valley High School | 2004-2008 |
|-----------------------------|-----------|
|-----------------------------|-----------|

Diploma

Origin Coding Academy 2018

certificate of completion

## **Employment History**

Albertsons 2007-2012

courtesy clerk/ cashier/ service deli tech/ night crew stocker/ produce clerk/ dairy clerk

Over the course of my employment here I worked in various departments. Most of them involved stocking shelves efficiently while still greeting customers and providing excellent customer service in a timely, friendly manner.

Home Front Pest Control 2012-20014

pest control technician

With this job I mainly worked alone as I spent the entire day driving from home to home treating our customers with their various pest problems. This taught me the value of time management as I had a set list of services to complete each day without any management supervision.

Bulls Eye Pest Control

pest control technician

Same overall job description and experience as Home FrontResume

Brian Connors

31011 Jedediah Smith Rd

Temecula, CA. 92592

seahorse8789@gmail.com

#### Summary

I have worked in the retail and pest control industry for a combined 11 years now. With those careers I have developed customer service and time management skills to complete projects on time. However, neither of these careers were not satisfactory to me. With that being said, I have decided to go back to school to learn computer programming.

Education

Temecula Valley High School 2004-2008

Diploma

Origin Coding Academy 2018

certificate of completion

**Employment History** 

Albertsons 2007-2012

courtesy clerk/ cashier/ service deli tech/ night crew stocker/ produce clerk/ dairy clerk

Over the course of my employment here I worked in various departments. Most of them involved stocking shelves efficiently while still greeting customers and providing excellent customer service in a timely, friendly manner.

Home Front Pest Control
pest control technician

2012-20014

With this job I mainly worked alone as I spent the entire day driving from home to home treating our customers with their various pest problems. This taught me the value of time management as I had a set list of services to complete each day without any management supervision.

Bulls Eye Pest Control
pest control technician
Same overall job description and experience as Home Front

2014-2018

2014-2018